ZEIN IRFANSYAH

WEB DEVELOPER (LARAVEL, REACT JS)

62895613982082 | 12.zeinirfansyah@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/zein-irfansyah | zeinirfansyah.me | Tasikmalaya, Indonesia

SUMMARY

Fresh graduate of Informatics Department, University of Technology Yogyakarta, with a GPA of 3.78 and 1 year of intern experience in web development. Possesses a high level of enthusiasm and skills in software engineering and digital technology honed through various software development projects and organizational activities. Specializes in web development using Laravel and React JS. Has good discipline, high loyalty, and integrity. Highly motivated to work anywhere and capable of working under pressure.

EXPERIENCES

Project-Based Intern: Frontend Virtual Internship Experience Core Initiative (April 2023 – May 2023)

- Successfully implemented design concepts into web applications using Vue JS.
- Developed unit tests in Jest to guarantee the quality of code.
- Learned the fundamentals of CI/CD.

Web Developer Intern SMK Daarul Abroor Tasikmalaya (April 2022 – March 2023)

- Building and developing a web-based library information system using PHP and MySQL.
- Engaged in the maintenance and development of a library information system website.

Volunteer Committee KSPM Goes to School – KSPM UTY (March 2022 – April 2022)

- Created a poster design for the "Goes to School" events.
- Developed a concept for virtual zoom backgrounds and certificates.

EDUCATION

University Of Technology Yogyakarta (2019 – 2023)

S1 Informatics, 3.78/4.00 GPA

- Thesis: Android-Based Mapping Application for Yogyakarta Tourism Object with Geotagging and LBS.
- Intern member of Kelompok Studi Pasar Modal Organization.

CERTIFICATIONS

- Create Web Applications with React Dicoding Indonesia (November 2023)
- Create Front-End Web for Beginners Dicoding Indonesia (November 2023)
- The Basics of JavaScript Programming Dicoding Indonesia (October 2023)
- The Basics of Web Programming Dicoding Indonesia (September 2023)
- Applications & Use Cases Professional Certification Altair RapidMiner (Agustus 2023)
- React JS Web Frontend Development Bootcamp Sanbercode (March 2023)
- The Complete Java Programing –Udemy (April 2021)
- PHP & MySQL Certification Course YouAccel (November 2020)
- Web Development Beginners Bootcamp Udemy (Juny 2020)

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Web Development

Proficient in developing and implementing REST API in web applications using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, ReactJS, and PHP.

Database Management

Capable of developing both SQL and NoSQL databases.

REST API Implementation

Capable of integrating REST API into web applications.

UI/UX Design

Able to design user interfaces with Figma by applying user experience principles.

SOFT SKILLS

- Problem Solving
- Analytical Thinking
- Teamwork and Collaboration
- Task and Time Management
- Creativity
- Fast Learner

LANGUAGE PROFICIENCY

Bahasa Indonesia: *Native* English: Intermediate